A Finding Aid to the Susan Conway Gallery Records, circa 1928, circa 1940s-2003, bulk 1987-2003, in the Archives of American Art AAA.susacong
Archives of American Art
- Client Files, 1987-2003; Series 2; 1.85 Linear feet Boxes 8-10, 26
  - Evans, Walter, Oliver Harrington, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Fain, Deborah, Brece Honeycutt, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Farrar, Dennis B., Pat Oliphant, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Fiegel, Sheryl, MetLife, 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Fisher, Colin, ArtChicago 2002, Dorothy Dehner Prints (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Fisher, Laura and Chester, 1998-2002 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Forbes Magazine, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - The Freedom Forum, 1993-1996 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Freidenrich, Jill, 1999-2002 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Fruitlich, Chris, Pat Oliphant, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Gardner, Ted, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Gibson, Tom, AT&T, 1991-1992; 1999 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Gilot, Françoise, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Goode, David, Norfolk Southern Corporation, 1993-1999 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Gowdey, Peter, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Elizabeth Hague Interior Design, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Hallmark Cards (Box 9)
    - Acquisitions, 1989-1993 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Binney & Smith, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Rountree, Melissa, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Hartman, Deborah C., Pat Oliphant, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Haskell, Preston, 1997; 1999 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Healy, Patrick, Mrs., 1998 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Hechinger, John W., 2000 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Highfield, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Hirshhorn, Olga, 1991-1997 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Holt, Karen, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Idema, James, Leonard Baskin, 1994-2002 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Idema, James, Pat Oliphant, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Jacobson, Leonard, Mr. and Mrs., 1990s (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Jessup, Claudia, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Johnson, Haynes, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Leunell, David and Bob Fishko?, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Kahn, Michael, 1998-2001 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Keane, Thomas, Dorothy Dehner, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Kesselman, Mickey and Linda, Pat Oliphant, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Kotz, Mary Lynn and Nathan K., Dorothy Dehner Sculpture, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Kraushaar Galleries, 1989-1991 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Kuhn, Lisa, U.S. State Department, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Madigan, Michael, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Maguire, Cary/L.C., 1993-1997 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Maher, Jamie, Mary Ellen Doyle, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Maliksen, Frank, Will Barnet, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - McGann, Al, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - McIntyre, Dee Ann, Pat Oliphant, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - McLaughlin, Ann, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - McMillan, Eleanor, Eric Aho, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - McSweeny, William F., 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Miller, Elizabeth and Steve, Mary Ellen Doyle and Susan Davidoff, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Mitchell, Andrea, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Mizel, Steve, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Moore, Kim, Sam Scott, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Museum of Art Fort Lauderdale, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Myers, Shirley, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Naughton, James M., The Poynter Institute, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Nelson, Stebbins, ArtChicago 2002, Mary Ellen Doyle (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Norrell, Julia, William Christenberry, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - The Open Studios, Six Artists Submitted, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Orlando Museum of Art, Sue Scott, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - O'Rourke, P.J., 2002 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Orr, David, Silverman Purchase, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Osborne, Richard, Eric Aho, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Palmer, Philip W., ArtChicago 2002, Sam Scott (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Philip Morris (Box 9)
    - Contract, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Hay Adams Installation, 1994-1997 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - (Jan. 20, 1997), 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Knox, George, 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Phillips, Gifford, Pat Oliphant Purchase from Santa Fe Exhibition, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Pincus, Ann T., Pat Oliphant Lithograph Out on Approval, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Pomeranz, Judy, Sam Scott Out on Approval, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Price, Carter (Denver, CO), 1999 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Prochnow, Pam, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Prospective Clients, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Rabinowitz, Harriet, ArtChicago 2002, Leonard Baskin Lithograph (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Reisman, Eugene, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Ritzenberg, Allie, 2000; 1998 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Safer, Morly, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Sallie Mae, 1988-1997 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Samet, Gertrude, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Sasakawa Peace Foundation, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Scholl, Jane, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Schulner, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Sego, Mickey, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Shaffer, Stephen, Pat Oliphant Lithograph, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Shapiro, Gabriel, Mr. and Mrs., Pat Oliphant, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Simikic, A.J., 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Socks, James, Dr., 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Southwest Texas State University, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Steiner, Anna and Ernest, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Stone, Flo and Roger, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Such-Baer, Marianne, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Swinsky, Morton, 1990-2000 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Tsatsos, Moya, 1998-2001 (Box 9, Folder 86-87)
  - Tsatsos, Moya, Pick-up of Brilliant Corners, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Tsatsos, Moya, Edward Sorel, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Vickers, Sam, 1987-1999 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Villa, John, Katja Oxman, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Wainwright, Susan, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Wallace, Renee, ArtChicago 2002, Dorothy Dehner (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Washington Area Lawyers for the Arts, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Weir, Mathew and Ann, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - The Wexler Group, 1992-2000 (Box 10, Folder 7-11)
  - Williams, Ralph W., Mr. and Mrs., 1998 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Woldenberg, James R., The Axe, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Woldenberg, Nadine and Rick, 1999-2002 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Yarbrough, Sidney, Dr. and Mrs., Dorothy Dehner, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Youmans, Anne Brooks and Cesar Rudzki, Eric Aho, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Restricted Folder (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Exhibition and Loan Files, 1987-2003; Series 3; 0.85 Linear feet Boxes 10-11
  Exhibitions and loans are documented through correspondence with clients, galleries and artists; inventories; notes; press releases; price lists; sales receipts; and shipping records. The records found here are not comprehensive; additional documentation regarding exhibitions and loans can be found in Artists’ Files, and the bulk of Pat Oliphant exhibition material is found in Series 4.
  Folders are arranged chronologically by exhibition date.
  - "John McLaughlin Annual Staff Show" (Dec. 1987 - Jan. 1988), 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - "A Preview of Four Washington Artists" (Jan. - Feb. 7, 1988) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - "Elements Architectural" (June 14 - July 3, 1988) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - "Landscapes" (July 5-24, 1988) (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - "Yellow + Gold" (July 26 - Aug. 14, 1988) (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - "Quintet" (Aug. 16 - Sept. 4, 1988) (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - "James McLaughlin Memorial Staff Show" (Dec. 6, 1988 - Jan. 7, 1989) (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - "Preview: 1989" (Feb. 14 - Apr. 8, 1989) (Box 10, Folder 24-25)
  - "Gallery Artists: New Work" (July 11 - Aug. 8, 1989) (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - "Seven From Manhattan" (Sept. 17 - Oct. 5, 1991) (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - "Etchings and Design Bindings" (Oct. 8 - Nov. 2, 1991), 1988-1991; 1996 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - "Summer 1992: Flowers and Landscapes" (June 20 - July 11, 1992) (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - "Presidential Campaign '92" (Oct. 6-31, 1992) (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - "Presidential Campaign '92," The Princeton Club of New York (Nov. 9-28, 1992), 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 31-32)
  - "Human Rights," Franklin Square Exhibition Space (Nov. 17 - Dec. 10, 1993) (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - "Christenberry, Holden, Raftery, Rice" (June 14 - July 15, 1994), 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - "Full Circle: A Holiday Show of 10 Washington Artists" (Nov. 29, 1994 - Jan. 13, 1995) (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - "Worth a Thousand Words," The Walters Art Gallery (1995) (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - "VII+I" (Dec. 12, 1995 - Jan. 20, 1996), 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - "Small Treasures" (Dec. 12, 1996 - Jan. 17, 1997) (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - "Survey" (Dec. 2, 1997 - Jan. 17, 1998), 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - "Spring Preview" (Feb. 18 - Mar. 14, 1998) (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - "The Other World of Oliphant" (Mar. 18 - Apr. 25, 1998) (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Chuck Corn Book Signing (May 6, 1998) (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - "Blue Ribbons" (June 9-30, 1998) (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Summer Exhibitions, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Judy Bass, Brece Honeycutt and Page Allen (Sept. 22 - Oct. 17, 1998) (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - "Deck the Walls" (Dec. 8, 1998 - Jan. 9, 1999) (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Meridian International Exhibitions, "Outward Bound" (1999) and "True Colors" (2002), 1999-2002 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - "On Exhibition: A Review" (Mar. 23 - Apr. 10, 1999) (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - "Southern Exposure," The Columbus Museum (Autumn 1999 - Canceled) (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - "Deck the Walls" (Nov. 9, 1999 - Jan. 8, 2000) (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - "Gardener's Delight," The National Museum of Women in the Arts (May - Aug. 2000), 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Brece Honeycutt, Charles Reid and Sam Scott (June 27 - Sept. 16, 2000) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - "Autumn: A Selection of Gallery Artists and Oliphant's Presidents and Supporting Cast" (Sept. 26 - Oct. 21, 2000) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - "Deck the Walls" (Dec. 1, 2000 - Jan. 20, 2001) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Meridian International Center, "True Colors" Traveling Exhibition, 2001-2003 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Group Show (Through May 2001) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Summer Exhibitions, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - "Deck the Walls" (Dec. 15, 2001 - Jan. 2002), 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - "Early Spring", 2002 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - "Found Treasures" (July 28 - Aug. 1, 2002) (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Records Regarding Patrick Oliphant, 1976-2003; Series 4; 11.5 Linear feet Boxes 11-22, 26, OV 27
  This series documents the exhibitions, promotion and sales of artist and political cartoonist Patrick Oliphant though correspondence with clients, galleries, and museums regarding exhibitions and sales; inventories and lists; publicity portaits and slides of an installation; press clippings; sales invoices; shipping records; writings; and other miscellaneous records. Extensive documentation is found on the following traveling exhibitions: "Oliphant: The New World Order in Drawing and Sculpture," "Oliphant's Presidents: 25 Years of Caricatures," and "Seven Presidents." The bulk of Oliphant client files are found in Series 2.
  The series is arranged as 4 subseries.
  4.1 General Files, 1978-2003
  4.2 Exhibition and Loan Files, 1987-2003
  4.3 Press Files, 1976-2003
  4.4 Photographs, 1980s-2003
  - General Files, 1978-2003; 4.1
    Materials may overlap with those in subseries 4.2.
    Folders are arranged alphabetically by folder title.
    - Achenbach Foundation for Graphic Arts, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - American Heritage, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - American Red Cross Quilt, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Andrews and McMeel, Reagan Book, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Archives of Southwestern Writers, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Artist's Archives, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - ArtNews, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - The Association of American Editorial Cartoonists, 2000; 1987 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - AT&T, 1989-1993 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Atkin, Louis, 1998-2001 (Box 11, Folder 20-23)
    - Atkin, Louis, Additions (2001), 2000 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Atkin, Louis, The Clinton Collection, 2000-2002 (Box 11, Folder 25-31)
    - Australian-American Education Leadership Foundation, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Auth, Tony, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Bad Golfers Association, circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Bechtler Gallery (Charlotte, NC), 1991 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Biography, U.P.S., 2003 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Bronze Sculpture, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Brooklyn Museum of Art, 1999-2002 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - BSI (Becker Special Interest, Inc.), 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Bush Presidential Library, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Business-Higher Education Forum (Feb. 8-11, 1996), 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - California, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Campaign Buttons, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Cartoon Art Museum (San Francisco, CA), 1994; 1996 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Cartooning, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Cartoons: AT&T, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Cartoons: Campaigns, circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Cartoons: International Trade, Economics, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Cartoons: Nixon Inventory (1969 - May 30, 1991), circa 1991 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Cartoons: Russia, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Cartoons in Private Collections, 1991-1994 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - The Cat Cabinet (Amsterdam), 1993; 1997 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Chicago Public Library, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Click Imports, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 54)
      Contains original artwork
    - Conrad, Kay, League of Women Voters, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Corporate Magic, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Correspondence, 1988-2001 (Box 11, Folder 57-58)
    - Corrigan, Mary Beth, AFL-CIO, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Craven, Carol, Sculptures Sent on Loan, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Cuba, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Deaton Museum Services for Ronald Reagan Library, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - DeLeon, Sylvia [ Mr. Speake r Pedestal], 1998 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Donations, 1992-2000 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Durrin Productions, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Eaton, John and Pat Oliphant (George Washington University; June 8-10, 1995), 1993 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Edmund Muskie Archive and Library, 1994-1999 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Ellsworth, Bob, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Essays, circa 1990s (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Etherington Conservation Center, 1997-2002 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Exhibition Proposals in the Past, 1995-2000 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - The Fixer, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - The Forbes Magazine Collection, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Four Seasons Hotel, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Gerald R. Ford Presidential Library and Museum, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Gerald R. Ford Presidential Library and Museum (Box 12)
      - Eisendrath, Charles, 1993-1995 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Hooker, Robert, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 19-20)
      - Old Checklist (Mar. 30, 1996) (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Getlein, Frank, "Oliphant on Nixon" Book Proposal, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Herblock, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Hill, Draper, 2001; 1999 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Hirschfeld, Al, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Hoover Institution Stanford Booking, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Huntington Library, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Inauguration, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - India (New Delhi), Sudhir Tailang, 2000; 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Indyck, Jill, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Inquiries, 2000-2001; 1992 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - International, 1990-1993 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - International Arts and Artists, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Inventory Report, circa 1990 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Invoices, 1988-1990; 1998 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Jack Nelson Legal Fellowship Dinner (May 1997) (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Japan, Leads, circa 1994 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Japan, Lee Kimche McGrath, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Japan, Takeda, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Japanese, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Jimmy Carter Library, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Jimmy Carter Library, Bradley Hale, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Johns Hopkins, Sylvia Eggleston Weir, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Kiev (Summer 1996) (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Landau Nast Foundation, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Landfall Press, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Letters, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Letters, Fanmail, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Letters, In Offense, 1987-1993 (Box 12, Folder 49-50)
    - Library of Congress (Box 12)
      - Current, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 51)
      - Osborne, Betty, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 52)
      - Permanent Collection, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Lindburg, John, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Long Range Plans, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Los Alamos National Laboratory, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Lyndon Baines Johnson Library, 1993-1996 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Mailing List, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Maudlin, Bill, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Meurer, Tom, Ross Perot, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Michigan Journalism Fellows, 1991-1994 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Michigan Journalism Fellows (1993), Charles Eisendrath, 1992-1997 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Michigan State University, Dean William Allen, 1997; 1995 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Midwest Museum of American Art, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Millbrook Press, Book Cover, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989-2003; 1978 (Box 13, Folder 3-5)
    - Mississippi Museum, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - The Munson Gallery, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - The Munson Gallery, Damaged Works, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Museum of Art Fort Lauderdale, Gallery Visit (4/18/98), 1998 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - N.A.I.C.A., 1997 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - National Academy of Sciences, Bronze Portrait, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - National Archives, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - The National Foundation for Caricature and Cartoon Art, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - The National Gallery of Caricature and Cartoon Art, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - The National Portrait Gallery, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - The National Portrait Gallery, Gift, Wendy Reaves, 2000-2002 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Needle, Josh, Impolitic Cartoon Commentaries, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - New York Public Library, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - The New York Times (Mar. 13, 1991), 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - The New York Times Magazine (July 14, 1990) (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Newseum, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Nixon Sculptures, Whittier College, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Norton, David C., Judge, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - un nouveau Musée...pour rire, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - The Ohio State University, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Oliphant Family, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Oliphant/Tom Gibson PBS Project, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - One Time Use Fees and Permits, 1992-1997 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Paris, 1992-1994 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Peace Links, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Pedestals and Hoods (Vitrines), circa 1991 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Permission to Reproduce, 1999-2003 (Box 13, Folder 32-34)
    - People Magazine, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Perrot, Paul, Santa Barbara Museum, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Phillips, Gifford and Joann, Santa Fe Fine Arts Museum Gift, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - The Phillips Collection, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - The Phillips Collection, "Daumiere's Legacy in Modern Life" Lecture, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Playboy Magazine, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Possible/Future Exhibitions, 1994-2000 (Box 13, Folder 41-51)
    - Postcard "I Have Returned" (1st Order - 2000 - Aug. 1992), circa 1990s (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Poster, circa 1991 (Box 13, Folder 53-54)
    - Poster Promo, circa 1991 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Poynter Institute, Sculpture Exhibition (2002), 1999-2002 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Prints, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Prints, Clients, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Prints, Signed and Available, circa 1990s (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Promotional Blurbs (Historical), 1990s (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Promotional Blurbs and Ideas, 1989-1991 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - Public Affairs Television, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Publicity, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Quotes, circa 1990s (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Reproductions Credit Requirements, circa 1990s (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - Research Request, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - The Richard Nixon Library and Birthplace, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Rinehart, Jonathan, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Ritzenberg, Albert, Mr. and Mrs., 1999 (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Rockwell Museum (Corning, NY), 2001 (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - Rolling Stone Magazine, 1984-1986 (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Rolling Stone Press, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 72-73)
    - Rolling Stone Press, Wayne Kline, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - The Ronald Reagan Presidential Library, 1989-1992 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
    - Ruskin, Steve, Greater Talent Network, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - The Saatchi Gallery, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Sacramento and San Francisco, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Sales, 1989-2001 (Box 14, Folder 6-8)
    - Sales, Santa Fe, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Sales, Sculpture, circa 1991 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Sales Letters, Press Releases, Blurbs, Etc., 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Samples of Print-Outs and Reviews, 1989-1992 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Schulz, Charles, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Scuba Diver Print Documentation, 1993; 1991 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Sculpture Catalog, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Sculpture, Interest In, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Sculpture and Packing Slips, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Sculpturing, General, 1982-1985 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Searchinger, Gene, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - "Seven Presidents" Exhibition, Reference Only - SCC, 1990s (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Signature, circa early 1990s (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Souter, David, Supreme Court Justice, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Stanford Museum, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - The State, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Sternburg, Fred, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Sulgrave Club, 1997; 2000 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - The Sun Sentinal Sculpture Awards, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Swarthmore College Library, 1981-1985 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - "Talk and Draw" AV Requirements, circa 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - "Talk and Draw," Festival Australia (The Kennedy Center; Oct. 16, 1994) (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Tamarind Institute, 1993-2000 (Box 14, Folder 31-32)
    - Tamarind Institute, Investors (Sept. 1993), 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Tampa, Design for Exhibition, circa 1992 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Tasende Gallery, 1992-1997 (Box 14, Folder 35-37)
    - Telfair Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1996; 1994 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Thomas Nast Award, 1999; 1992 (Box 14, Folder 39-40)
    - Thomas Nast Award and Draper Hill, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - The Today Show (NBC), 1991 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Todd Street Productions, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Travel, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Travel Ideas (Articles), 1987-1993 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - United States Supreme Court, 1990-1998 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - UPI, 1990s (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Video, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Washington College (Chestertown, MD), 1997 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Washington Convention Center Proposal, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Washington Speakers Bureau, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Washington University (St. Louis, MO), 1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - "Wattoons" by L.E. Johnston, circa 1980s (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - WETA, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Wood, J. Arthur, circa 1990s (Box 15, Folder 8)